（忆往昔）
传说 猎人 记录者
The lore, hunters, man of letters,
都是扯淡
all of them are crap.
我是恶魔
I'm a demon.
如今试图找回你哥哥已经毫无意义了
There's no point in trying to bring your brother back now.
现在说话的根本不是真正的你
This isn't even the real you I'm talking to.
绝对是真正的我
Oh, it's the real me, all right.
欢迎回来 迪恩
Welcome back, Dean.
- 你还好吗 - 我挺好
- How you doing? - I'm good.
但我需要工作
But I need to work.
如果出了岔子
If things go sideways…
哪怕是一点差错
I mean, like, an inch,
你必须告诉我一声
you gotta give me the heads-up.
没问题
Done.
我们要去干活儿了
We got work to do.
那是什么 鬼魂 恶魔
What is it? Spirits? Demon?
- 怎么 - 这不可能
- What? - This can't be possible.
龙 老兄
Dragons, dude.
我们要抓的是灯灵
We're hunting a djinn.
灯灵吗
A freaking geni!
那你是什么
Well, then, what are you?
吸脂怪
I'm a pishtaco.
喜直怪
A fish taco?
不是类人机器人
It's not a mandroid.
是易形者
It's a shapeshifter.
吸血鬼海盗
Vampire pirates?
吸血海盗
Vampirates.
- 蓝精灵 - 是小精灵
- Smurfs? - Fairies.
小精灵
Fairies?
有乳头耶
Nipples?
拜托
Come on.
讨厌
Bitch!
幻象怪需要很多的精神能量
Tulpas require a-a ton of psychic energy.
不是幻象怪
It's not a tulpa.
是卡利奥佩
It's Calliope.
我想我知道我们要对付的是什么了
I think I know what we are dealing with here.
那是超巨魔童（电影鬼马小精灵中的白色胖鬼）
It's the Stay Puft Marshmallow Man.
（如今）
（康涅狄格州 新迦南）
好了
Now, now.
我知道今天很沉痛
I know it's a terribly sad day.
邦妮·拉克鲁瓦是个好女人
Bunny LaCroix was a good woman,
是个心慈仁义的主顾
a fair employer with a kind heart.
但我们还要工作
But there is work to be done.
不到24小时内
In less than 24 hours,
拉克鲁瓦家族就会来到这里
the LaCroix famiy will descend upon this estate.
参加葬礼 听遗嘱宣读
for the funeral and the reading of the will,
我们要确保别墅一切井然有条
and it is our duty to make sure this manor's in tip-top shape.
这是我们欠邦妮的
We owe that much to Bunny.
科洛蒂
Colette.
打扫主衣物间
To the master closet.
你去选出拉克鲁瓦太太下葬的衣物
I'd like you to select Mrs. LaCroix's wardrobe for the burial.
奥利维亚
Olivia.
务必确保所有厕所都一尘不染
Please make sure all the lavatories are spotless.
为什么要我…
Why do I have to…
够了
Now, now.
你还是新雇员
You're still the new hire.
科洛蒂要比你有资质
Colette has seniority.
快去吧 没时间浪费了
Chop-chop. There's no time to waste.
但是…
But…
你已经死了啊
Y-you're dead.
你做了什么啊
What have you done?
[邪恶力量 第10季第6集]
给你
There you go.
单独煮的
Individually brewed.
科技改变生活啊
Technology, man.
真汉子不喝这么小杯的
Real men don't drink out of cups this small.
什么味儿的 肉桂卷吗
What is that… "Cinnamon roll"?
是糖霜甜甜圈
It's, uh, "Glazed donut."
如果你不想要
Look, man, if you don't want it, I…
没事的
Nah, it's… got it.
警用频道或内网上有情况吗
So, any leads on the scanner or the…interweb?
没有 连猫上树都没有
Nothing… not even a cat up a tree.
这么说我们打算重出江湖
So right when we're ready to jump back into it,
江湖却一片风平浪静
it, uh, goes radio silence.
墨菲定律
Murphy's law.
他就是个二货
Well, Murphy's a douche.
想绕路去康涅狄格州一趟吗
Hey, feel like taking a detour to Connecticut?
什么
What?
我做清理的时候发现的
Found it while I was dustbusting.
我们的吗
One of ours?
鲍比的
It's one of Bobby's.
总共有27条留言
And, in total, 27 messages.
唯一有意思的是两天前的一条
The only one that counts is from two days ago.
鲍比是一位邦妮·拉克鲁瓦的遗嘱受益人
Apparently, Bobby's been named a beneficiary in Bunny LaCroix's will.
邦妮谁
Bunny LaWho?
律师说她是位女继承人
Attorney said she's an heiress,
鲍比本人或其近亲要去一趟新迦南
and Bobby's presence or next of kin is being requested in New Canaan.
我觉得我们算得上
I figured we qualify.
鲍比怎么会认识女继承人啊
How did Bobby know an heiress?
鲍比也有秘密
Bobby had secrets, man.
比如喜欢托瑞·斯培林（女演员）
Like loving on Tori Spelling.
如果他知道迪恩劈腿该多难过
If he only knew Dean cheated on her.
走吗
Anyway, road trip?
说不定鲍比给我们留下了买酒钱
Who knows? Maybe Bobby earned us some beer money.
我们穿得是不是不够隆重
Think we're a little underdressed?
联调局那身就在后箱里
I mean, the fed threads are in the trunk.
开玩笑吗
You kidding me?
我们终于有一次不用穿西装了
For once, we don't have to wear suits.
幸好我的腰带不是弹性的
You're lucky my waistband's not elastic.
有事吗
May I help you?
我是萨姆·温彻斯特 这是迪恩·温彻斯特
I'm Sam Winchester. This is Dean Winchester.
我们代表鲍比·辛格前来
We're here on behalf of Bobby Singer.
辛格先生不能来了吗
Mr. Singer won't be coming?
不能 他去世了
No. He passed away.
真遗憾
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
你也节哀顺变
Uh, condolences for your loss, too.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们刚刚错过葬礼
Well, you just missed the funeral,
但家里人都在里面休息 你们请进吧
But the family's relaxing inside, if you'd like to join.
容我介绍萨姆和迪恩·温彻斯特
Allow me to introduce Sam and Dean Winchester.
你们是韦斯切斯特的温彻斯特家族的人吗
Sam and Dean Winchester of the Westchester Winchesters?
不是的
U-uh, n… no.
我们应该没有…
I don't think there's…
- 没有 - 什么关系 抱歉
- Nah. - …any relation. Sorry.
没事
No matter.
你们俩…
You two are…
好可爱
…adorable.
我是海蒂 邦妮的亲戚 这是我妹妹贝弗利
I'm Heddy, Bunny's cousin, and this is my sister, Beverly.
荣幸
Charmed, I'm sure.
那是邦妮的小弟弟
And that's Bunny's youngest brother,
斯坦顿 喊他斯坦就好
Stanton… "Stan" for short.
请进吧 伙计们
Come on in, fellas.
一起哀悼吧
Join the mourning.
和他的小新娘 安珀
And his child bride, Amber.
加油 斯坦
Go, Stan!
别这样 你都打扰我注意力了
Babe, don't. You're breaking my concentration.
还有戴什 家里最小的
And then there's Dash. That's the baby of the family.
他是邦妮的曾侄 哈佛商学院的
He's Bunny's great-nephew… Harvard business.
你们怎么认识邦妮的
How do you guys know aunt Bunny?
我们
We, uh…
我们其实并不认识她
We… we… we didn't personally know her.
我们的干爹 鲍比·辛格认识她
Our… our surrogate dad, Bobby Singer, did.
对
Did.
鲍比 没听说过
Bobby? Never heard of him.
但你们周末可以跟我们讲讲
But you can fill us in over the weekend, huh?
周末
The weekend?
律师没说吗
Didn't the attorney tell you?
今天举行葬礼 明天宣读遗嘱
Service was today, and the reading of the will tomorrow.
你们可以在这里过夜
Oh, but you're welcome to spend the night.
所有房间都是双人的
All the rooms sleep two.
三个人也行
Or three.
好嘞
Okay.
科洛蒂哪去了
Where's Colette?
她辞职了
She quit.
可怜的姑娘对拉克鲁瓦太太的死伤心欲绝
Poor dear was so distraught over Mrs. LaCroix's passing.
于是去寻找自我了
Went off to find herself.
去印度修行了吗
Ashram in India?
萨拉索塔一家小丑学院
Uh, clown college in Sarasota.
明智
Good choice.
五分钟后能去大堂跟二位说两句吗
May I have a word with you in the hall in five minutes?
- 嗯 - 当然
- Sure. - Yeah.
那么 萨姆
So Sam…
跟我说说
tell me…
你锻炼吗
do you…work out?
荣幸
Charmed, I'm sure.
这些什么人啊
What are these people?
应该是叫做权贵
I think they're called W.A.S.P.S.
什么
What?
抱歉刚刚没明说
My apologies for being so oblique back there,
但我是为了你们好
but I'm doing you boys a favor.
好吧
O-okay.
你们也知道
As you know,
拉克鲁瓦太太给辛格先生留了点东西
Mrs. LaCroix bequeathed something to your Mr. Singer.
但明天遗嘱才会宣读
But the reading of the will isn't until tomorrow,
我不希望你们要被迫留下
and I would hate for you to have to stick around.
跟主人家…交际
and be forced to… well, mingle with the family.
没事 管家先生
Don't worry, Alfred.
我们知道哪个叉子是吃虾用的
We know which one the shrimp fork is.
算是吧
Kind of.
温彻斯特先生
Oh, Mr. Winchester.
如果你的意思是 我觉得你们不配
If you're implying that I don't think you're good enough,
其实恰恰相反
i-it's quite the contrary.
你们太好了
You're far too good.
拉克鲁瓦家族是…
The LaCroix family is…well…
怎么礼貌点说呢
How shall I say this politely?
一群贪财的吸血鬼
…money-grubbing leeches.
什么意思 我以为他们都是权贵呢
What are you talking about? I thought they were all loaded.
的确 但并不有钱
Loaded… yes. Rich… no.
他们都遭受了经济衰退的打击
The recession hit every one of them,
如果他们知道了邦妮给你们留下了什么
and I'm afraid if they knew what Bunny left you,
这些秃鹰会企图抢财产
those vultures would try to stake claim.
因为律师好心同意提前把东西拿来
And since the attorney kindly agreed to a hand-off,
你们就不必遭受他们的刺探了
you don't have to be subjected to their scrutiny.
你知道邦妮和鲍比怎么认识的吗
Do you have any idea how Bunny and Bobby knew each other?
完全不知道
Not in the slightest.
如果没别的事了
Um, now, if there's nothing else,
我让奥利维亚送你们出去吧
shall I have Olivia show you out?
不用 我们自己认路 谢谢
No, no. That's, uh… we got it. Thanks.
这么花哨的东西居然留给鲍比
Kind of fancy to leave a guy like Bobby.
你跟我想到一起去了吗
You thinking what I'm thinking?
邦妮跟鲍比有一腿 这些石头是真的
If Bunny was banging Bobby, then maybe these rocks are real.
不是真的吗
What do you mean it's not real?
那老太太可有钱了
The old bag was rolling in it.
看来那老太太是喜欢
Well, looks like the old bag's got a soft spot.
假红宝石和方晶锆石
for fake rubies and cubic zirconium.
这倒是有点意思
This is interesting, though.
是把钥匙
It's a key.
什么的钥匙
A key to what?
想知道只有一个办法
There's one way to find out…
去问管家
ask Jeeves.
贝弗利看见你晚餐时发色情短信了
Beverly saw you sexting at dinner.
贝弗就是胡说八道
Bev doesn't know what the hell she's talking about.
我是在给我妈发短信
I was texting my mom.
发一个剥开香蕉的表情吗
An emoticon of a peeled banana?
她喜欢水果
She likes fruit.
承认吧 你出轨了
Just admit it… you're cheating.
你喝醉了
And you're drunk.
而且还多疑
Not to mention paranoid.
跟兰斯一样
Just like Lance.
他总说可怜的邦妮跟别人上床
He was always accusing poor Bunny of sleeping around.
因为她的确有
Because she was.
我姐姐就是个穿香奈儿的下贱婊子
My sister was nothing but a two-bit hooker in Chanel!
你好大胆
How dare you.
你姐姐都死了
Your sister's dead.
你看什么看
What the hell are you looking at?
你俩都死得好
Good riddance to you both.
斯坦顿
Stanton.
干什么
What?!
我没说话
I didn't say anything!
斯坦顿
Stanton.
不要
No! Aah!
一切都好吗
Everything okay?
不太好
Not really.
- 嗯 - 谢谢
- Yeah. - Thanks.
你们二位是落下什么了吗
I presume you gentlemen left something behind?
我会去衣橱找找…粗麻布
I'll check the front closet for…burlap.
告诉你 管家先生
I got news for you, Mr. Belvedere…
我这身是帆布的
The Jacket's canvas.
二位之前来过吗
Uh… you two were here earlier?
对 你是谁
Yeah. Who wants to know?
霍华德警探 新迦南警局
Detective Howard, New Canaan P.D.
恭喜二位
Congratulations, boys.
你们现在正式是凶案嫌疑人了
You're now officially murder suspects.
抱歉 什么
I'm sorry. What?
邦妮·拉克鲁瓦的弟弟斯坦顿今晚被杀了
Yeah, Bunny LaCroix's brother Stanton was killed this evening.
他的尸体刚运去停尸房
His body's just gone to the morgue.
- 你觉得… - 我不知道该怎么想
- And you think… - I don't know what to think.
所以二位
And that's why you two.
和其他今天来过这栋别墅的人
and anyone else who stepped foot in this house today.
都要被扣留接受审问
is being detained for questioning.
贝弗利 放开我 显然是她干的
Beverly, let go of me! It's so obvious she's guilty.
你疯了 老太婆
You're off your rocker, old lady.
「老太婆」 我…
"Old lady"?! I…
我才39岁
I'm 39.
自03年就是了
And you have been since '03.
你好大胆
How… how dare you.
抱歉打扰了 你说是谁干的
I'm sorry to interrupt, but… but who's guilty?
那个骚货 安珀 是她杀了斯坦
The town slut, Amber. She killed Stan.
她什么动机呢 大侦探
And what's her motive, "Murder, she wrote"?
大家都知道安珀在到处乱搞
Oh, everyone knows that Amber was sleeping around.
她想离开斯坦 但她的婚前协议十分牢固
She wanted to leave Stan, but her prenup was ironclad,
于是她就杀了他
so she killed him.
听上去挺合理
Sounds logical.
除非你们相信
Well, unless you believe.
她的那套可笑的说辞
that ridiculous story that she's been peddling.
「一个鬼魂杀了斯坦顿」 真是的
"A ghost killed Stanton"… honestly.
鬼魂
Uh, a-a ghost?
她说是邦妮过世的丈夫 兰斯做的
She's claming that Bunny's late husband, Lance, did it.
你们听过这种事吗
Have you ever heard such a thing?
这可笑 蠢成这样
What a panic! So stupid.
你因为那些合成激素 脑子都不正常了
You're nutty as a squirrel on those synthetic hormones.
「不正常」 你真过分
"Nutty"? How appalling of you.
哈佛不教礼貌吗
Don't they teach you manners in Harvard?
看来我们遇上桩案子啊
So, uh…looks like we might have a case here.
- 复仇鬼魂 - 嗯
- Vengeful spirit? - Yeah.
我们能去车里拿电磁干扰仪吗
Think we can get to the car, get the EMF?
那个警探盯着呢 不可能
Not with, uh, detective friendly. Not a chance.
我们只能采取老办法了
Guess we're gonna have to go old-school.
- 好吧 找冷点 - 嗯
- All right. Cold spots it is. - Yeah.
你留下盯着虚荣女
You stay here, keep an eye on Mrs. Peacock.
- 和高帅富 我去四处看看 - 嗯
- and colonel mustard. I'll sniff around. - All right.
告诉你 我已经有一艘漂亮的大游艇了
For your information, I already own a big, beautiful yacht.
你管那东西叫游艇吗
Oh, is that what you call that thing?
好吧 是红木单帆船
Fine. It's a mahogany sunfish.
我得说 作为刚刚失去两个家庭成员的家庭
Got to say, for a family that just lost two members,
你们似乎都没什么事
you all…seem fine.
萨姆 我告诉你个家族秘密吧
Well, Sam, I'll let you in on a little family secret.
我们不怎么喜欢彼此
We don't really like each other.
不过 哪个家庭喜欢彼此呢
Then again, what family does?
我家人就是
Mine does.
差不多吧
For the most part.
现在只有我和哥哥相依为命了
It's just my brother and me, so…
那你很幸运
Then you're lucky.
相信我 这样算奇迹了 我们在一个屋檐下
Trust me… it's a miracle we've been under the same roof.
待了24小时还没…
for 24 hours and haven't…
不该这么说
My bad.
你为什么这么确定不是安珀干的
And, uh, w-why are you so sure Amber didn't do it?
安珀不是杀人的人
Because Amber's not a killer.
她连用无线网络都不怎么会
She has trouble using wi-fi.
我觉得她是杀不成人的
I don't exactly think she's capable of murder.
她说的那个鬼魂的故事呢
And her story about the ghost?
我不相信鬼魂
I don't believe in ghosts.
但是 如果有人会阴魂不散
That said, if anyone would come back to haunt,
那一定是兰斯叔叔了
it's uncle Lance.
听说他人很坏
Heard he was a real bastard.
他死了没人心疼
No one really mourned his death…
除了邦妮姑妈 他死后她闭门不出
Except aunt Bunny, who became a recluse after he died.
或许那老家伙有什么不满
So, maybe the old goat has a chip on his shoulder.
谁知道呢
Who the hell knows?
戴什
Dash…
该你了
You're up.
迪恩
Dean?
奥利维亚
Olivia?
谢天谢地 我以为你是他
Thank god. I thought you were him.
谁
Him who?
菲利普 那个管家
Phillip… the butler.
他把我锁了起来 因为我不肯撒谎
He locked me in here because I wouldn't lie.
对警探隐瞒我看到的事
to the detective about what I saw.
你看到什么了
What did you see?
我看到他用毯子把科洛蒂的尸体裹了起来
I saw him roll Colette's body in a rug.
去小丑学院的科洛蒂吗
Clown college Colette?
管家杀了她
The butler killed her?
不不 他只是藏尸
No, no. He just… he just hid her.
那是谁杀了她
Then who killed her?
我知道听上去很疯狂
I know this is gonna sound crazy,
但我是亲眼所见
but I saw it with my own eyes.
我猜猜
Let me guess…
兰斯的鬼魂
Lance's ghost.
不
No.
是邦妮
Bunny's.
那个 失陪一下
You know what? Uh, excuse me.
别啊 留下嘛
No, no, stay.
怎么样
So?
看见管家了吗
You seen the butler?
没有 怎么了
No. Why?
因为如果有人知道是怎么回事 那就是他
'cause if anybody has answers, it's him.
这里有两个复仇鬼魂
We're dealing with two vengeful spirits.
看来邦妮姑妈也有怨愤
Apparently, aunt Bunny had a bee in her bonnet, as well.
夫妻鬼魂杀人组吗
Husband-and-wife tag-team killer ghosts?
婚姻总得想办法维系
Well, got to keep the marriage alive somehow.
这把钥匙 通往一间隐藏的阁楼
The key… is to a hidden attic.
邦妮为什么要把阁楼的钥匙给鲍比
Why would Bunny want Bobby to have a key to her attic?
不知道 还有更怪的
I don't know. It gets weirder.
我发现奥利维亚和科洛蒂都锁在里面
I found Olivia and Colette locked inside.
小丑学院的那个
Clown college Colette?
嗯 但她没去学扎气球动物 她死了
Yeah, but she ain't studying balloon animals. She's dead.
管家跟这些事有什么关系
Now, what does the butler have to do with all this?
是他把她们锁在里面的
He's the one who locked them in there.
我不知道为什么
Now, I don't know why,
但他在掩盖鬼魂的罪行
but he's covering for the spooks.
做他们的忠仆
He's acting like their Renfield.
好吧 我们得找到他
All right. We got to find him.
- 我看楼上 你看楼下 - 好的
- I'll take upstairs. You take down here. - All right.
萨姆·温彻斯特
Sam Winchester?
你跑哪去了
Where did you run off to?
哎呦呦
Well, well, well.
这是什么情况
What do we have here?
你为什么在这里鬼鬼祟祟的
Whatcha doing snooping around these halls, hmm?
没安好心吧
Up to no good?
我们一起做点坏事吧
Why don't we get up to no good together?
要知道人说年纪越长的女人越会做
You know, they say women just get better with age,
就像好酒 或干酪一样
like a fine wine or… or cheese.
我不耐乳糖
U-uh, I-I… uh, I'm lactose-intolerant, so…
得了 萨姆
Oh, come on, Sammy.
别这么扭捏
Don't be coy.
据我接受盘问还有10分钟
We have got a good 10 minutes before my interrogation,
你这样年轻的小伙子10分钟肯定能干不少事呢
and I bet a young buck like you can do a lot in 10 minutes.
你先请
I'm right behind you.
「我先请」
"Right behind me."
帮我拉下拉链好吗
Could you just give me a hand with this zipper?
我总是拉不开
I always have such a hard time…
（管家房间）
那边有个水龙头漏了
Uh, leaky faucet's down the hall.
少跟我闲扯了
Cut the crap, Wadsworth.
你为什么把死去的女仆藏在密室里
What are you doing hiding dead maids in secret rooms?
我知道看上去很奇怪
I know it all looks rather…peculiar,
但我能解释
but I can explain.
你把科洛蒂的尸体藏在了阁楼里
So, you hid Colette's body in the attic.
好让她不抢走邦妮的风头
so that she wouldn't steal Bunny's thunder?
我不想让拉克鲁瓦太太的葬礼上
I couldn't stand the thought of overshadowing.
再出桩人命 吸引走大家的注意力
Mrs. LaCroix's funeral with another death.
她应该体面接受送别 这是我欠她的
She deserved a proper farewell. I owed it to her.
你真是疯了
Well, that's crazy.
不 温彻斯特先生 这是忠诚
No, Mr. Winchester. That's loyalty.
（萨姆 找到了菲利普的尸体）
- 迪恩 - 萨姆
- Dean. - Sam.
- 嗯 - 不是鬼
- Yeah? - It's no ghost.
- 什么 - 是易形者
- What? - It's a shapeshifter.
这个易形者以装死人为乐吗
So, the shifter's getting its jollies by impersonating dead people.
对 先是邦妮 然后是兰斯 菲利普
Yeah. First Bunny, then Lance, now phillip.
看来可以排除是「管家干的」
Guess we can rule out "The butler did it."
那个变态刚刚蜕了皮 现在可能是任何人
And the creep just shed, so now it could be anybody.
甚至是你
Even you.
或者是你 我们得找银具
Or you. We need to find some silver.
天呐
Oh, my god!
我们发现他时他就这样了
He was like that when we found him.
是谁干的
Who did this?
我们还不知道
We don't know yet, okay?
听我说 冷静点
Now, listen. Calm down.
我知道你以为他是跟鬼魂一伙儿的
I know you think he was working with ghosts,
但其实情况要糟得多
but there's something way worse going on here.
还糟…
Worse than…
到底是怎么回事
What is going on?
如果你想帮忙 就帮帮我们
If you want to help, then help.
你能做到吗
Can you do that?
你们要银器干什么
Why do you need the silverware?
自卫
For protection.
用黄油刀吗
Butter knives?
相信我们 我们这是有道理的
Trust us … there's a method to our madness.
你能拿一下这个吗
Can you, uh, hold this?
迪恩
Dean.
好了
All right.
开始吧
Let's do this.
不行
No.
No! Ugh.
等等 上一个 他有座岛
Wait, wait, wait. Go back. He owned an island.
还有兔唇呢
And a harelip.
要是他能让你在富丽堂皇的地方
Well, who cares if he's ugly.
喝迈代鸡尾酒 谁在乎他丑不丑
if you're drinking mai tais in the lap of luxury?
你们好 女士们
Hey. Hey, ladies.
你们在干什么
What are you doing?
给贝弗利挑男人
Trying to find Beverly a man.
我现在都在网上钓男人
I've resorted to fishing online.
因为现实中有些人不肯咬钩啊
because the live ones won't bite.
你是说刚才的事吗
You mean back there?
我只是在欲擒故纵
I-I was just playing hard-to-get.
好吧 那么
Well, then…
你演得还真像
You're a very convincing actor.
过来
Come.
好
Sure.
好咧
All right.
坐这儿
Sit here. Yes.
讨厌 我觉得我被冷落了
Boo. I'm feeling so left out.
过来吧 亲爱的
Well, then, uh… come on in, darling.
欢迎你
Water's warm.
好极了
Yes.
真的假的
Really?
我们可以解释的
We…can explain.
我猜猜 去年圣诞你们空虚难耐 就好上了
Let me guess. You two got bored last Christmas.
其实是在新迦南的海滨宴会上
New Canaan Clambake, actually.
我们在吃自助餐 软壳蛤没了
We were in line at the buffet, they ran out of steamers,
一来二去就…
one thing led to another, and, well…
但是我们没有杀斯坦顿
But we didn't kill Stanton.
我们虽然有婚外情 但我们没有杀人
We may be guilty of cheating, but not murder.
- 摸一下这个 - 什么 为什么
- Touch these. - What? Why?
快照做 不然我就把海滨宴会的事全说出来
Do it, or I go cards-up on your whole Clambake.
我们 通过了吗
Did…we pass?
是的
Yep.
别担心 我不会说出去的
Don't worry. Your secret is safe with me.
走吧 你们俩
Come on, you two.
看看他手指多长
Did you see how long his fingers were?
你看见没 多长
First of all, did you see this? Look how long.
要等你们完事儿了我再过来吗
Should I come back when you're done?
他在叫我 我就
Oh, he's … he's … he's calling to me, so…
真是一场好戏啊
And it's all going to hell right here, right now.
抱歉打扰你雅兴了
Sorry to interrupt.
不是她们
"Grey Gardens" Cleared.
也不是戴什和安珀
Okay, well, so is Dash and Amber.
不过他们在偷情
They're a thing, by the way.
是啊 权贵们啊
Y… Yeah. W.A.S.P.S.
所有人都在这儿了
Well, so, that's everyone.
除了…
Except for …
这可好 又多了个淹死的
Well, we got a floater.
好极了
Great.
他死了
Yeah, he's a goner.
淹死在马桶里 脏死了
Drowned in a toilet? How filthy!
什么样的禽兽才干得出这种事
What kind of monster would do such a thing?
别看我啊 我只是来小解的
Don't look at me. I was just trying to pee.
行了 先别急着互相指责
Okay, hold on. Before we start pointing fingers …
安珀有动机
Amber has motive.
她杀了警探
She killed the detective.
因为她知道他迟早会查出
because she knew that it was just a matter of time.
是她杀了斯坦
before he figured out she killed Stan.
太棒了 神探 这就破案了
Bravo, Rizzoli. You solved the case.
你也想猜猜看吗 妙女
Want to weigh in, too, Isles?
斯坦顿和警探都不是我杀的
I didn't kill Stanton or the detective,
我有证据
And I have proof.
行了
Okay, guys …
我的不在场证明就在这里
My alibi is in this room.
有好戏了
Ooh. Wait for it.
安珀没有杀警探 因为她那时候跟我在一起
Amber couldn't have killed the detective, 'cause she was with me.
我们相爱了
We're in love.
我们有私情
We're… sleeping together.
- 我就知道 - 那你也有动机了
- I knew it. - Well, then, you have motive, too.
你杀了斯坦因为你在跟他老婆偷情
You offed Stan because you were diddling his wife.
老太婆话太多了
Ohh. The old lady doth protest too much.
你指责我们只是为了撇清你自己的嫌疑
You're only pointing the finger to distract from your own guilt,
搞不好这恶女就是你的帮凶
and you probably got baby Jane to help.
你好大胆 我先走了
Well, I never! I'm leaving!
等一下
All right, hang on.
首先 话要好好说
First of all, who talks like that?
其次 所有人都不许走
Second of all, no one's leaving, okay?
把你的手拿开 小伙子
Oh, get your hands off me, young man.
听好了 我不相信任何人
Okay, see, I don't trust anyone,
你走只会加重你的嫌疑
And leaving just makes you look guilty.
迪恩说得对 现在已经死了四个人了
Dean is right, okay? We have four corpses now.
死了四个人
Four corpses?
对 你可以把菲利普和科洛蒂也算上
Yes. You can add Phillip and Colette to the list.
去小丑学院的科洛蒂吗 我以为她…
Clown College Colette? But I thought …
她死了 好吗 她死了
She's dead, all right? She's dead.
你们要是还一直
And we can't help you.
互相指责的话 我们是帮不了你们的
unless you stop arguing with one another.
你们必须相信我们
You need to trust us.
相信你们
Trust you?
我们根本不认识你们
Uh, we don't even know you.
听着 我跟你说实话
Look, buddy, I'm trying to be objective here,
我们家的问题一向是数都数不清
but we've had countless family functions before,
一天到晚恨不得杀了对方
and even though we wanted to kill one another,
但我们从没那么做
we never did.
没错 我们的家庭聚会从不会以谋杀结束
Dash is right. Our get-togethers never end in murder.
与以往唯一不同的是你们来了
The only thing different this time around is you.
慢着 首先
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Okay, first of all, whoa.
不管你在暗示些什么
Whatever you're suggesting …
你们两个
You two!
走吧
Let's go.
想都别想
Don't even think about it.
我猎过野鸡
I…hunt pheasant.
在警察来之前给我坐好了
Sit tight until the cops get here.
你不会想这么做的
You don't want to do this.
你们要想活着出去只能靠我们
We are your best shot at making it out of here alive.
我们不是坏人 戴什
We're not the bad guys, Dash.
恕我不敢苟同
I beg to differ.
你还穿着法兰绒呢
You're wearing flannel.
有钥匙
Keys.
不行 是从外面锁上的
No, it's locked from the outside.
你逗我呢吧
Are you kidding me?
棒极了
Great.
「台湾制造」 该死的不锈钢
"Made in Taiwan." Freakin' stainless steel.
这就是没有人被烧伤的原因吗
So that's why no one sizzled?
这些都不是真的银
They're not even real silver?
先是方晶锆石 然后是这个
First, cubic zirconium, and now this.
怪不得富人都还那么富
No wonder the rich stay rich.
我们要怎么杀了这东西
How we gonna kill this thing?
我们车后箱里有银弹
You know, we got silver bullets in the trunk.
前提是我们能从这里出去
Yeah, assuming we ever make it out of here.
我不明白 萨姆和迪恩为什么要杀我们
I don't get it. Why would Sam and Dean want us dead?
这还不明显吗
Isn't it obvious?
他们想夺取我们的遗产
They wanted our inheritance.
我猜邦妮姑妈留给他们的东西不够多
Guess whatever aunt Bunny left them wasn't good enough.
看在上帝的分上 戴什
For the love of god, Dash,
在你杀了谁之前放下那把枪
Put down the gun before you kill someone!
没关系的
It's okay.
我可是…猎过…野鸡的
I…hunt…pheasant.
放下
Put it down!
他俩开着那辆美国车来的时候
I knew those boys were trailer trash.
我就知道他们不是什么好东西
the moment they rolled up in that American-made.
而且还是同性恋
Not to mention homosexuals.
同性恋杀人犯
Ugh. Homosexual murderers.
就像利奥伯德和勒伯（电影《迷魂索》的两位男主角）
Like Leopold and Loeb.
只不过这两位更性感
Only hotter.
马上去报警
Oh. Call the police at once.
我看还是免了
Oh, I don't think so.
你说什么 小姑娘
Excuse me, young lady?
不管有没有凶手 你都还在上班
Killer or no killer, you're still on the clock.
你们这群蠢货真是错的离谱
You idiots couldn't be more wrong …
全都弄错了
About everything.
你们难道不知道
Don't you know.
假如凶手不是管家 那就是女佣了吗
if it's not the butler, it's the maid?
迪恩
Dean?
快来看看
You got to see this.
我们被那个女佣耍了
We got played by the maid.
两扇门都是加固过的
Both doors are reinforced.
我不是女佣
I'm not the maid.
怪不得你打扫得不干净
Well, that explains the dust.
我是邦妮的女儿
I'm Bunny's daughter.
你说什么呢 邦妮没有孩子
What are you talking about? Bunny didn't have a child.
不 她有 还是个非常孝顺的女儿
Oh, yes, she did … a very devoted one.
我爱母亲胜过一切
I loved mother more than anything,
比你们任何一个人都爱
which is more than I can say for any of you.
那你这些年都躲在哪里
Then, where have you been hiding all these years?
阁楼上
The attic.
和电影里一样
Like in the movie.
安珀
Oh, Amber.
除了妈妈之外
Outside of mother,
菲利普是这栋宅子里唯一的知情人
Phillip was the only one at the manor who knew.
所以她去世之后
So after she died,
他可怜我 就把我放出来了
he took pity on me, and he let me out.
他让我装作是新来的女佣
He told me to pose as the new maid.
这样我就能藏在你们眼前了
so I can hide in plain sight.
这就是你杀了科洛蒂的原因
That's why you killed Colette …
为了得到她的工作
for her job?
不不不 科洛蒂的死只是个意外
Oh, no, no, no, no. Colette was just an accident.
我只是想吓吓她
I just wanted to scare her.
因为我发现她偷东西
because I caught her stealing.
这也没法解释你为什么想杀死我们
Well, that doesn't explain wanting us dead.
我们都不是贼
None of us are thieves, huh?
不 你们更坏
On, no. You're worse.
你们的贪婪 鄙弃
Your greed, your disdain,
公然不尊重母亲
your blatant disrespect for mother …
这是你们自找的
Oh, you all had it coming!
但为什么杀了菲利普呢
But…why kill Phillip?
既然他站在你那边
I mean, if he was on your side…
因为他背叛了我
Because he turned on me.
斯坦顿死后 他把我锁了回去
After Stanton, he locked me back up.
幸运的是 那个可爱的小傻瓜放我出来了
Lucky for me, the cute, dumb one let me out.
武器库
Gun safe.
试试这个
Try these.
难怪你会被锁起来 你是个怪物
No wonder you were locked away. You're a monster!
这你就不了解了
Oh, you have no idea.
怎么回事
What in god's name …
闭嘴
Shut up!
待在这里
Stay here!
还有人尿了吗
Did anyone else wet themselves?
你瞄不准我
You don't have a clear shot.
你也一样
Neither do you.
杀死你的快感 会仅次于杀死鲍比·辛格
Killing you is the next best thing to killing Bobby Singer.
你和鲍比有什么恩怨
What's your beef with Bobby?
首先 他杀了我父亲
For starters, he killed my father.
兰斯是易形者
Lance was a shifter?
兰斯不是我父亲
Lance wasn't my father!
我母亲和易形者偷情
Mother had an affair with a shifter.
怀了孕 她告诉兰斯我是他的孩子
She got pregnant, told Lance I was his.
他信了
He bought it…
直到她从医院把我带回来
Until she brought me back from the hospital.
我真正的父亲在那里等着
My real dad was waiting.
兰斯奋力抵抗 但他不是易形者的对手
Lance put up a fight, but he was no match for a shifter.
就在我父亲要带走我时
And just as my dad was about to take me…
猎人变成了猎物
…the hunter became the hunted.
鲍比
Bobby.
鲍比杀死我父亲后 又要杀我
After Bobby killed my father, he came after me.
母亲求他饶过我
Mother pleaded with him to spare me.
他同意了 但提出了一个条件
He agreed … under one condition.
她要一直锁着你
That she keep you locked up.
确保我和其他人的安全
For my safety and the safety of others.
母亲告诉其他人 她的孩子没了
Mother told the family she lost the baby.
她把我锁在阁楼上
And she locked me in the attic.
但是她自始至终都为我付出
But she remained devoted to me until the very end …
甚至让鲍比同意
Even got Bobby to promise.
若她遭遇不幸 他就照顾我
to take care of me if anything happened to her.
等等 鲍比饶了你
Wait a minute. Then, Bobby spared you.
你应该心存感激
You should be grateful.
感激什么
For what?!
感激他让我一辈子被关着
Keeping me locked up my whole life?
杀了我会更仁慈
It would have been kinder to kill me.
奥利维亚
Olivia…
你没必要这么做
You don't have to do this.
做怪物是一种选择
Being a monster is a choice.
这个选择 有人很久之前就替我选了
That choice was made for me a long time ago.
你为什么还不开枪
Why haven't you taken a shot?
你没有银子弹了 是不是
You don't have any silver bullets, do you?
是的
Yes, officer.
是的 非常感谢
Yes, thank you very much.
是的 不会错
Yes, no, you can't miss it.
在街道尽头的大房子
Big house on the end of the street.
好的 再见
All right. Bye, now.
两位
Guys?
警察马上就来
Police are on their way.
好个乱子
What a mess.
我欠你们一个道歉
I owe you two an apology.
没关系
Don't sweat it.
你只是为了保护家人
I mean, you were just protecting your family,
这没什么错
and…there's nothing wrong with that.
我和邦妮姑妈的律师通了电话
So, I spoke to aunt Bunny's attorney.
他说除了吊坠
He said, outside from the pendant,
所有一切都留给了奥利维亚
everything was left to Olivia.
那个
Hey, you know what?
说到这事
Speaking of that…
你们应该留着这个
…you guys should keep it.
这是阁楼钥匙
It's a key to the attic.
鲍比一定对邦妮姑妈非常重要
Bobby must have really meant something to aunt Bunny.
我们该怎样报答你们
How can we repay you?
这样吧
You know what?
忘了我们来过就行
Just forget we were ever here.
但你们救了我们
But you saved our lives.
我想让大家都知道你们多么英勇
I want everyone to know what heroes you …
伙计 我们救下你们
Look, pal, the fact that we pulled your bacon out of the fire.
和别人无关 明白吗
is nobody's business. Okay?
说真的 伙计
I'm serious, Izod.
别再提了
Put a pin in it.
不然我们会回来找你算账的
Or we'll come back for your preppy ass.
迪恩 你刚刚是怎么回事
Dean, what was that all about back there?
你说什么
What are you talking about?
多余的那几枪
I mean… all those extra shots.
易形者已经死了之后的那几枪
after the shifter was already dead.
那是怎么回事
What was that?
不知道 打靶练习
I don't know. Target practice?
别这样 说真的
Come on, man. I'm serious.
你确定那不是…
You sure it wasn't…
我说不上来 残留的恶魔或是和血印有关
I don't know, demon residue or something to do with the mark or …
不是
No.
都不是
No, none of that.
好吧
Right.
我得说实话
Look, man, I got to be honest …
天哪 萨姆
Oh, my god, Sam.
这是我…恢复后第一次杀人
It was my first kill since I've been back.
我有点焦虑
You know, I got a little anxious.
我想要确保自己没做错什么 就这么简单
I wanted to make sure it was done right … plain and simple.
就是
It's …
我为什么还要解释
Why am I even explaining this to you?
迪恩 我
Dean, I …